A Guide to the Fritz Albert Lipmann papers, Rockefeller University Faculty FA123
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Correspondence, 1950-1986; 2; 13.25 Cubic Feet
  - ["S"], 1969-1970; 1 of 2 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - ["S"], 1969-1970; 2 of 2 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Salas, Maria L. (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Schweiger, Manfred (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - ["T"], 1969-1970 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Tao, Manano and Pearl (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - ["U"], 1969-1970 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - ["V"], 1969-1970 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - 1969-1970 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Tao, Manano and Pearl (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - ["U"], 1969-1970 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - ["V"], 1969-1970 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - ["W"], 1969-1970; 1 of 2 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - ["W"], 1969-1970; 2 of 2 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - ["X-Y-Z"], 1969-1970 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - ["A"], 1971-1973 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - ACS Garvan Medal (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Argentina (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Aspen meeting (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - ["B"], 1971-1973; 1 of 3 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - ["B"], 1971-1973; 2 of 3 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - ["B"], 1971-1973; 3 of 3 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Bauer, Karl (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Biochemistry (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Biochemistry Ninth International Congress (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Biophysics Congress (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Book correspondence, 1 of 3 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Book correspondence, 2 of 3 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Book correspondence, 3 of 3 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - ["C"], 1971-1973 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Calif (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Cold Spring Harbor (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Cold Spring Harbor, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Copenhagen, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - ["D"], 1971-1973 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - ["E"], 1971-1973 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Evins, Warren H. (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - ["F"], 1971-1973 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - FEBS meetings, Bulgaria, 1971; 1 of 2 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - FEBS meetings, Bulgaria, 1971; 2 of 2 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - ["G"], 1971-1973 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Germany, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Gordon, Julia (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - ["H"], 1971-1973 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Historical development of bioenergetics, 1 of 3 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Historical development of bioenergetics, 2 of 3 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Historical development of bioenergetics, 3 of 3 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - ["I"], 1971-1973 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Institut de la Vie meeting (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - ["J"], 1971-1973 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - ["K"], 1971-1973; 1 of 2 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - ["K"], 1971-1973; 2 of 2 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Karolina Symposium (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Kleinkauf, Horst (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - ["L"], 1971-1973 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - ["M"], 1971-1973; 1 of 2 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - ["M"], 1971-1973; 2 of 2 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - McClean Hospital Scientific Advisory Committee (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - ["N"], 1971-1973 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - ["O"], 1971-1973 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - ["P"], 1971-1973 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - ["Q"], 1971-1973 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - ["R"], 1971-1973 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Richter, Dietmar (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Roskoski, Robert, 1 of 3 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Roskoski, Robert, 2 of 3 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Roskoski, Robert, 3 of 3 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Ryan, Gordon A. (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - ["S"], 1971-1973; 1 of 3 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - ["S"], 1971-1973; 2 of 3 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - ["S"], 1971-1973; 3 of 3 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - ["T"], 1971-1973 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Table Ronde Roussel Uclaf (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Table Ronde Roussel Uclaf - Origin of Life, 1 of 2 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Table Ronde Roussel Uclaf - Origin of Life, 2 of 2 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - ["U"], 1971-1973 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - ["V"], 1971-1973 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - ["W"], 1971-1973; 1 of 3 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - ["W"], 1971-1973; 2 of 3 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - ["W"], 1971-1973; 3 of 3 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - ["X-Y-Z"], 1971-1973 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - ["A"], 1974-1975 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - ["B"], 1974-1975; 1 of 2 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - ["B"], 1974-1975; 2 of 2 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Biochemistry (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Brandeis University (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - ["C"], 1974-1975 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - CIBA (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - ["D"], 1974-1975 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - ["E"], 1974-1975 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - ["F"], 1974-1975 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - ["G"], 1974-1975 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - ["H"], 1974-1975 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - ["I"], 1974-1975 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - ["J"], 1974-1975 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - ["K"], 1974-1975; 1 of 2 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - ["K"], 1974-1975; 2 of 2 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - ["L"], 1974-1975 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Library of Congress (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Lipmann birthday (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Lynen birthday (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Lipmann Symposium-Berlin, 1974; 1 of 3 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Lipmann Symposium-Berlin, 1974; 2 of 3 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Lipmann Symposium-Berlin, 1974; 3 of 3 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - ["M"], 1974-1975; 1 of 3 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - ["M"], 1974-1975; 2 of 3 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - ["M"], 1974-1975; 3 of 3 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - MIT Gramicidin S project (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - ["N"], 1974-1975 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Nobel meeting (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Nobel Foundation, 1 of 2 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Nobel Foundation, 2 of 2 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - ["O"], 1974-1975 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Ochoa Symposium, 1975; 1 of 3 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Ochoa Symposium, 1975; 2 of 3 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Ogawa, Yasuo (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - ["P"], 1974-1975 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - ["R"], 1974-1975; 1 of 2 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - ["R"], 1974-1975; 2 of 2 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - ["S"], 1974-1975 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Salk Institute (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - ["T"], 1974-1975 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Table Ronde Roussel - Biomolecular Evolution, 1 of 3 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Table Ronde Roussel - Biomolecular Evolution, 2 of 3 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Table Ronde Roussel - Biomolecular Evolution, 3 of 3 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Table Ronde Roussel - Brain Oligopeptides, 1 of 2 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Table Ronde Roussel - Brain Oligopeptides, 2 of 2 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Tenth International Congress of Biochemistry (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - ["U"], 1974-1975 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - ["V"], 1974-1975 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - ["W"], 1974-1975 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - ["X-Y-Z"], 1974-1975 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - ["A"], 1976-1978 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Akers, Hugh (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Anke, Timm (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - ["B"], 1976-1978; 1 of 2 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - ["B"], 1976-1978; 2 of 2 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - ["C"], 1976-1978; 1 of 2 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - ["C"], 1976-1978; 2 of 2 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Chou, T. (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - ["D"], 1976-1978 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - ["E"], 1976-1978 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - ["F"], 1976-1978 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Friedman (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Fukami, Yasuo (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - ["G"], 1976-1978; 1 of 2 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - ["G"], 1976-1978; 2 of 2 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - ["H"], 1976-1978; 1 of 2 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - ["H"], 1976-1978; 2 of 2 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Hebrew University (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - ["J"], 1976-1978 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - ["K"], 1976-1978; 1 of 2 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - ["K"], 1976-1978; 2 of 2 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Krebs, Hans (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Kundu, Balaram (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - ["L"], 1976-1978; 1 of 2 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - ["L"], 1976-1978; 2 of 2 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Lipmann 85th birthday (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - ["M"], 1976-1978 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Mizumoto, Kiyohisa (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - ["N"], 1976-1978 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - ["O"], 1976-1978 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Orden Pour le Merite (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Origin of Life (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - ["P"], 1976-1978 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - ["Q"], 1976-1978 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - ["R"], 1976-1978; 1 of 2 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - ["R"], 1976-1978; 2 of 2 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - ["S"], 1976-1978; 1 of 2 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - ["S"], 1976-1978; 1 of 2 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - ["T"], 1976-1978 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - ["U"], 1976-1978 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - ["V"], 1976-1978 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - ["W"], 1976-1978 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - ["X-Y-Z"], 1976-1978 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - ["A"], 1979-1980 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - ["B"], 1979-1980; 1 of 2 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - ["B"], 1979-1980; 2 of 2 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Brandeis University (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - ["C"], 1979-1980 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - ["D"], 1979-1980 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Decker, Stuart (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Deutsche, Akademie (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - ["E"], 1979-1980 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Eightieth birthday letters, 1 of 2 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Eightieth birthday letters, 2 of 2 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - ["F"], 1979-1980 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Heden, Lars-Olof (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - History of Biochemistry (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - ["I"], 1979-1980 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Institut de la Vie (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - International Society for the Study of the Origin of Life (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - ["J"], 1979-1980 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - ["K"], 1979-1980 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Kubota, Kou (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - ["L"], 1979-1980 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Lee, Sung G. (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Liu, Dr. Ming-Cheh (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Lipmann lectures (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Lynen Memorial, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - ["M"], 1979-1980 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - ["N"], 1979-1980 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - National Science Foundation (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Orden Pour le Mérite (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - ["P"], 1979-1980 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - ["R"], 1979-1980; 1 of 2 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - ["R"], 1979-1980; 2 of 2 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Rockefeller University Senate, 1 of 2 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Rockefeller University Senate, 2 of 2 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Roswell Park Institute (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - ["S"], 1979-1980 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Spector, Leonard B. (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - ["T"], 1979-1980 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - ["V"], 1979-1980 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - ["W"], 1979-1980 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Weiss (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - ["X-Y-Z"], 1979-1980 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Zhang, Zhao-Cheng, 1980-1982 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Stuart Decker, 1980s; 1 of 2 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Stuart Decker, 1980s; 2 of 2 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - 1980 September-1984 January, 1 of 3 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - 1980 September-1984 January, 2 of 3 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - 1980 September-1984 January, 3 of 3 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Paul Ehrlich, 1981; 1 of 2 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Paul Ehrlich, 1981; 2 of 2 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - 1984-1985, 1 of 2 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - 1984-1985, 2 of 2 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Requests for autographs (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - 1985 March-November, 1 of 3 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - 1985 March-November, 2 of 3 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - 1985 March-November, 3 of 3 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - 1985 March-November, 1 of 2 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - 1985 March-November, 2 of 2 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - 1985 December-1986 April, 1 of 2 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - 1985 December-1986 April, 2 of 2 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - 1986 February-May (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - 1986 June-August (Box 45, Folder 9)
- Lecture Files, 1948-1979; 3; 1 Cubic Feet
  Includes correspondence, lecture notes and transcripts, travel notes.
  Arranged in alphabetical order.
  - Boston lectures on phosphoproteins (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Calif. notes (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Chicago talk (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Cold Spring Harbor, 1963 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Cold Spring Harbor Symposium (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Columbia University lecture, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Energy-flux system (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Fifth Annual Symposium on Fundamental Cancer Research (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Fifth New York lecture (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - First Biology Harvard talk (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Formation of peptide bonds (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - German talks (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Harvard lecture, 1948 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Harvard lecture, 1953 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Harvard alumni day, 1954 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Second Harvard lecture, 1954 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Third Harvard lecture, 1954 (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - Lecture 9-Harvard Biology Department (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - Harvard lectures, 1956 (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - First Harvard lectures, 1956 (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - Second Harvard lecture, 1956 (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - Third Harvard lecture, 1956 (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - Fourth Harvard lecture, 1956 (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - Fifth Harvard lecture, 1956 (Box 46, Folder 24)
  - Sixth and Seventh lecture, 1956 (Box 46, Folder 25)
  - Last Harvard lecture (Box 46, Folder 26)
  - Israel lectures (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - First Israel lecture (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Israel lecture part 1 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Lectures 1, 2, and 3 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Lecture 1, 1954 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Lecture 2, 1954 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Lecture 5, 1954 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Lecture 6, 1954 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Lecture 7, 1954 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Lecture 8, 1954 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Lecture 9, 1954 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Lecture 10, 1954 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Lecture notes (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Mechanism of Glutathione, 1960 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Mitteilungen de Deutschen (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Montclair State College lecture (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - New Haven lecture (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Oak Ridge Symposium (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Oversigt over Selskabets Virksomhed (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Pasteur Talk, 1964 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Problem of protein synthesis (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Revised lecture, 1967 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - San Francisco lectures (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - San Francisco lectures 1-4 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - San Francisco talk, 1972 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Session on protein synthesis (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Setsuro Ebashi (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Smoker talk (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - South American lectures, 1963 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Student lecture notes (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Student lecture notes, 1964 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Student lecture notes, 1965 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Student lecture notes, 1968 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Sulfate activation lecture (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Woods Hole symposium (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Woods Hole talk (Box 48, Folder 17)
- Manuscripts and Notes, 1930-1985; 4; 17 Cubic Feet
  Correspondence, notes, rough drafts of published articles and autobiography.
  - Aarhies material (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Accounts paper seconds, 1 of 3 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Accounts paper seconds, 2 of 3 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Accounts paper seconds, 3 of 3 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Accumulation of Guanosine, 1 of 3 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Accumulation of Guanosine, 2 of 3 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Accumulation of Guanosine, 3 of 3 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Aceto-CoA-Kinase (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Acetyl-Coenzyme A synthesis (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Acetyl-Coenzyme A synthesis through Pyrophosphoryl (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Acetylation of Glutomic (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Acetylation of Hemoglobin (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - ACS publicity article (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Action of the thyroid (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Activation of amino acids (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Acetylation of hemoglobins (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Activation of Glycogen synthetase, 1 of 2 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Activation of Glycogen synthetase, 2 of 2 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Activation of ppGpp-3-Pyrophosphohydrolase (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Additional data on equilibria (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Adenosinphosphatanaloga als substrate (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - ADP-ATP exchange (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Amino acid activation (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Amino acid incorporation (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Amino acid incorporation (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Amino acid polymerization (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Amino acid transfer, 1 of 2 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Amino acid transfer, 2 of 2 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Amino acid transfer from sRNA (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Amino acid transfer from sRNA to microsome (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Amino acid transfer from sRNA to microsome (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Amino acid transfer from sRNA to microsome II (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Amino acid transport (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Amino acids and RNA (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Aminoacyl and tRNA (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Annual review of biochemistry (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Annual reviews drafts, 1 of 3 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Annual reviews drafts, 2 of 3 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Annual reviews drafts, 3 of 3 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Antibiotics contribution to the analysis of protein synthesis, 1 of 2 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Antibiotics contribution to the analysis of protein synthesis, 2 of 2 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Article on ACS (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - ATP-linked concentration of calcium ions, 1 of 2 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - ATP-linked concentration of calcium ions, 2 of 2 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - ATP-linked reactions (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - ATP-phosphate cycle (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Attempts at the formulation of some basic biological questions (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Attempts to map a process evolution, 1 of 3 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Attempts to map a process evolution, 2 of 3 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Attempts to map a process evolution, 3 of 3 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Attempts toward biosynthesis, 1 of 4 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Attempts toward biosynthesis, 2 of 4 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Attempts toward biosynthesis, 3 of 4 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Attempts toward biosynthesis, 4 of 4 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Bacterial amino acid polymerization, 1 of 2 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Bacterial amino acid polymerization, 2 of 2 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Bacterial production of antibiotic polypeptides, 1 of 4 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Bacterial production of antibiotic polypeptides, 2 of 4 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Bacterial production of antibiotic polypeptides, 3 of 4 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Bacterial production of antibiotic polypeptides, 4 of 4 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Bacteriophage T4 DNA (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Bericht Ubereine Ruckreise (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Bibliography of the Biochemistry Research Laboratory (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Biochemical function of B vitamins (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Biochemical Research Laboratory (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Biogenesis of membrane (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Biological sulfate activation and transfer (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Biological use of energy (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Biosynthesis of chondroitin (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Biosynthesis of Gramicidan S, 1 of 3 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Biosynthesis of Gramicidan S, 2 of 3 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Biosynthesis of Gramicidan S, 3 of 3 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Biosynthesis of guanosine tetraphosphate (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Biosynthesis of hemoglobins (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Biosynthesis of RNA (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Biosynthesis of the coat protein of Coliphage f2 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Biosynthesis of Tyrocidine (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Biosynthetic mechanisms (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Biotechnology of protein synthesis, 1 of 2 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Biosynthesis of guanosine tetraphosphate (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Biosynthesis of hemoglobins (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - Biosynthesis of RNA (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - Biosynthesis of the coat protein of Coliphage f2 (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - Biosynthesis of Tyrocidine (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Biosynthetic mechanisms (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Biotechnology of protein synthesis, 1 of 2 (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - Biotechnology of protein synthesis, 2 of 2 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Brodie paper (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Calcium (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - CAMP activation (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - CAMP and protein (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - CAMP-ATP Exchange (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - CAMP vs. Polymerization (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Carbamyl phosphate (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Catabolite repression (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Cell-free protein synthesis (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Cell proliferation rate and intracellular regulation (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Cellular regulation and malignant growth (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Chain termination in vitro (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Characteristics of Phosphoproteins, 1 of 2 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Characteristics of Phosphoproteins, 2 of 2 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Characterization of a ribosome (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Chemical and enzymatic synthesis (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Chemical evolution (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Chemicals information (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Chicago CoA papers (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Chloramphenicol and chlortetracycline (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Chloroplasts (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Citryl-l-Phosphate and the citrate cleavage reaction (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Citryl-phosphate (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Comparison and the hybridization of B. Subtilis and E. Coli (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Comparison of guanosine (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Competition between EF1 and EF2, 1 of 2 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Competition between EF1 and EF2, 2 of 2 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Coding and charging specifications of sRNAs (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Coenzyme A paper, 1 of 3 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Coenzyme A paper, 2 of 3 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Coenzyme A paper, 3 of 3 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Coenzyme A and biosynthesis (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Coenzyme Q₁₀ (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - CoA Symposium papers (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Correlation between physiological and chemical heterogeneity (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - CYAMP-charging (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Cyclic amp (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Chondroitin sulfate synthesis (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Chromosomal localization (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Colorimetric determination (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Comparison of amino acid, 1 of 2 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Comparison of amino acid, 2 of 2 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Content of cyclic 3, 5 adenosine (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Control of B-Blucosyl Transferase (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Coupled oxidative phosphorylation (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Coupling between phosphorylation (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - DEAE (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - DEAE Cellulose runs (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Derivation of acetyl and CoA (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Determination of an upper limit (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Diffusion data on CoA (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Direction of polymerization (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Discovery of creative phosphate (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Discovery of the adenylic acid system, 1 of 2 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Discovery of the adenylic acid system, 2 of 2 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Discussion on enzymatic and cell structures (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Disproportions created by the exponential growth of knowledge (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Divergence in reactivity, 1 of 2 (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Divergence in reactivity, 2 of 2 (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - DNA-dependent in vitro synthesis (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - DNA-directed synthesis (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Early enzymes of bacteriophages (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Ebashi experiments (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - E. Coli aminoacyl (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - E. Coli and B. Subtilis (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - E. Coli carbamoyl phosphate synthetase (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Effect of antibiotics (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Effect of borate on the Carbazoli reaction (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - [Effect of GTP] (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Effect of electrical and chemical stimulatin (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Effect of GTP concentration (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - Effect of magnesium (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - Effect of primary structure of phosphoprotein (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - Effect of univalent actions (Box 61, Folder 15)
  - Effects of cyclic AMP, 1 of 2 (Box 61, Folder 16)
  - Effects of cyclic AMP, 2 of 2 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Elongation Factor (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Embden-Meyerhof Cycle, 1 of 3 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Embden-Meyerhof Cycle, 2 of 3 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Embden-Meyerhof Cycle, 3 of 3 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - "Encounter" magazine (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Energy (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Energy and RNA, 1 of 2 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Energy and RNA, 2 of 2 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Energy cycles in living organisms (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Energy paper (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Energy supply system (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Enzymatic activation of sulfate, 1 of 3 (Box 63, Folder 1)